show2.me 2016-05-10

# show2me :: Privacy Policy

(Last Updated: 09.02.2015)

### 1\. Privacy Statement

www.yesheis.com (“Website”) and yesHEis Mobile App (“Mobile App”) (collectively referred to as “YHI”) are operated by CV Digital Pty Ltd ACN 169 709 808, an Australian registered company ("CV", "we", "our", "us").

This privacy policy sets out our policies relating to the collection and use of your Personal Information whilst you use YHI. We may vary this policy from time to time.

CV is committed to protecting privacy. We understand that visitors and users of YHI are concerned about their privacy, and the confidentiality and security of any Personal Information that is provided.

We will only disclose Personal Information in accordance with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (or other applicable law), the Australian Privacy Principles, our terms and conditions of use, and this privacy policy. If there is any inconsistency, the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (or other applicable law) will prevail to the extent of any inconsistency.

### 2\. Personal Information Collected By Cv

(a) Upon your registration with us we collect information about you in order to provide you with access to resources and YHI platform available through the Website. We collect non-identifying information as well as Personal Information from you directly when you first register and also from time to time thereafter if you provide us with additional information.

(b) Personal information is information or an opinion about an individual whose identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained from that information. Personal Information which we may collect includes, without limitation:

  * (i) your full name

(c) Other information collected by us, which may or may not be considered to be Personal Information includes, without limitation:

  * (i) your email address;
  * (ii) your age;
  * (iii) your geographic location

(d) Sensitive Information which may be collected by us includes, without limitation:

  * (i) your racial or ethnic origin;
  * (ii) your religious beliefs or affiliations;
  * (iii) your philosophical beliefs

and is only collected if you elect to provide that information to us. 

(e) Whenever users visit the Website, our servers automatically record information for statistical purposes about your usage of the Website such as:

  * (i) the type of browser used;
  * (ii) the referring URL;
  * (iii) the IP address;
  * (iv) the number and type of pages viewed;
  * (v) the date and time of visits; and
  * (vi) the exit URL.

This information we collect is not Personal Information and, in any event, remains anonymous. We do not link the anonymous information to any other Personal Information unless you have either registered with YHI or logged in at the time of use. Accordingly, if you have not identified yourself on the Website, such as by registering or logging in, we will not link a record of your usage of our Website to you personally.

(f) This personal information is collected in a variety of ways, such as by email, internet access, and by use of its products.

### 3\. Use Of Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some features of CV products.

### 4\. Purposes For Which Cv Collects, Holds, Uses And Discloses Personal Information 

(a) We use an individual’s personal information for the purposes for which it was collected, or a purpose related to the purpose for which it was collected, and otherwise for internal management and related purposes, which include:

  * (i) to improve the CV products, services and user experience;
  * (ii) to provide a product or service you have requested; and
  * (iii) to provide technical support to you to use CV products and services.

(b) CV automatically gathers information to monitor the use of its digital products and services. Most of the data we collected is aggregated, and this information is effectively anonymous to us.

(c) Sometimes you will be asked to confirm that you agree to a particular activity or the collection of your personal information for a specific purpose. Though CV usually collects aggregate data, we will make it clear to you if any information is being collected in a way that could personally identify you.

(d) We may disclose personal information for the purposes for which it was collected, and for purposes related to the purposes for which it was collected, including:

  * (i) to external service providers so that they can provide financial, administrative or other services in connection with the operation of our business;
  * (ii) as permitted under privacy laws; and
  * (iii) with the individual’s consent or if the individual would reasonably expect that their information would be passed to the person to whom the personal information is disclosed.

(e) Where practical to do so and permitted by law, you have the option of not identifying yourself or using a pseudonym, when dealing with CV in relation to a particular matter.

### 5\. Personal Information Held By Cv

(a) We take reasonable steps to protect all personal information which we hold (including your personal information) from misuse, interference, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

(b) We take reasonable steps to hold personal information securely in electronic or physical form.

(c) These steps include password protection for electronic files, securing paper files in locked cabinets and physical access restrictions.

(d) When no longer required, personal information is destroyed in a secure manner or deleted.

(e) We also take steps to ensure that the personal information we collect is accurate, up-to-date and complete. These steps include maintaining and updating personal information when we are advised by individuals that their personal information has changed. 

### 6\. Disclosure Of Personal Information To Overseas Recipients 

CV may disclose personal information to outsourced information technology service providers, including cloud computing providers and data storage providers, based overseas primarily located in the UK and USA.

CV will take reasonable steps to ensure such overseas recipients do not breach the APPs or are subject to laws or a scheme substantially similar to the APPs.

### 7\. Disclosure Of Information Via Other Platforms Or Services

(a) Some CV services may be integrated with external services, including social media networks. This may mean that information, for instance about your interests and activities, is tracked or pulled from other places (such as Facebook). If you are signed in to a CV service which is integrated with other media tools, this information may be available to others depending on the privacy settings you have in place on other platforms.

(b) CV may use Google Analytics to track your usage of the CV site. Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilises the data collected to track and examine the use of www.CV.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualise and personalise the ads of its own advertising network. Personal data collected by Google includes Cookie and usage data, which is processed in the USA. Find Google's privacy policy here: http://www.google.com.au/policies/privacy/.

(c) Our products may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

(d) CV has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services. Your ability to opt-out of a third party tool or platform will depend on the conditions governing your agreement with that third party.

### 8\. How To Access Personal Information About You

(a) If you are an individual who has provided personal information to CV, you may request access at any time to personal information we hold about you. Certain information will be able to be accessed via your user profile created upon registration and available through the Website. You may also request access by emailing the Privacy Officer at [australia@yesHEis.com](mailto:australia@yesHEis.com?subject=Privacy%20Query)

Depending upon the personal information you seek to access, you may be asked:

  * (i) to put your request in writing to verify your identity; and/or
  * (ii) to provide further details to assist CV in responding to your request in a timely manner.

(b) We will respond to a request for access to personal information within a reasonable period after the request is made.

(c) You may also request a correction be made to personal information about you held by CV by contacting the Privacy Officer at [australia@yesHEis.com](mailto:australia@yesHEis.com?subject=Privacy%20Query)

(d) You may also request a copy of this Privacy Policy from the Privacy Officer.

### 9\. How To Complain About A Breach Of The Apps

If you believe that we have used or disclosed your Personal Information in a manner which is contrary to this policy or otherwise breaches an applicable law, you may make a complaint to the Privacy Officer at [australia@yesHEis.com](mailto:australia@yesHEis.com?subject=Privacy%20Query). 

Complaints will be dealt with in confidence. Within 30 days of receipt of your complaint we will notify you in writing as to what action we propose to take in relation to your complaint and will provide you with details of what further action you can take if you are not satisfied with our response.

### 10\. Further Information 

For any further information about this policy please contact the Privacy Officer at [australia@yesHEis.com](mailto:australia@yesHEis.com?subject=Privacy%20Query) or write to: 

The Privacy Officer  
CV Digital Pty Ltd ACN 169 709 808  
2 Killick Street  
Kunda Park, QLD, Australia 4556
